[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these factors defines the medical condition known as anemia?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Decreased number of red blood cells", "Decreased oxygen-binding ability of the hemoglobin molecules in the blood", "Decreased quantity of hemoglobin in the blood"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What crime was the famous Casanova imprisoned for in 1755?", "correct_answer": "Witchcraft", "incorrect_answers": ["Theft", "Fraud", "Adultory"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This standup comedian became famous as the large Massachusetts man attacked by a mugger in the next to last episode of Seinfeld.", "correct_answer": "John Pinette", "incorrect_answers": ["Eric Bana", "John Caponera", "Jimmy Pardo"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Most tomato cultivars produce fruit that is red when ripe, but some produce unusual colors such as this one.", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Black", "Striped", "Multicolored"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "To which of these countries are the Sami people not indigenous?", "correct_answer": "Denmark", "incorrect_answers": ["Finland", "Russia", "Sweden"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What vegetable is used for the preparation of the Passion Cake, which probably originated in the United Kingdom?", "correct_answer": "Carrot", "incorrect_answers": ["Potato", "Tomato", "Cucumber"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In 1939 James Stewart didnt star in Its A Wonderful Life but in Its a Wonderful World.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was the name of the street on which the Grey Gardens estate was located?", "correct_answer": "Lily Pond Lane", "incorrect_answers": ["Mallard Way", "Pebblestone Drive", "Ocean View Avenue"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What actor portrayed God in the 2007 movie Evan Almighty, one of the priciest movies ever made?", "correct_answer": "Morgan Freeman", "incorrect_answers": ["Jim Carrey", "Denzel Washington", "Will Smith"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Nearly half of all human bones are in the hands and feet.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "e^(pi*i) +1 = 0 is an important formula, involving the key mathematical constant e, which is popularly known as what?", "correct_answer": "Eulers Equation", "incorrect_answers": ["Einsteins Equation", "The Hyperbolic Cosine Law", "Newtons Equation"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What weapon does Judy Hollidays character, Doris Attinger, use to wound her adulterous husband in the 1949 romantic comedy Adams Rib?", "correct_answer": "Gun", "incorrect_answers": ["Axe", "Knife", "Nail file"]}]